nissannews.com 2010-12-06

# Nissan/Infiniti News Room

Nissan appreciates your interest in its products and your visit to this website. Your privacy is important to us and we want you to feel comfortable visiting our sites. The protection of your privacy in the processing of your personal data is an important concern to which we pay special attention during our business processes. Personal data collected during visits to our website are processed by us according to the legal provisions valid for the countries in which the websites are maintained. In addition our data protection policy complies with Codes of Conduct applicable company-wide for Nissan. The Nissan websites may include, however, links to other websites that are not covered by this privacy statement. 

Nissan respects your privacy and personal sphere.

**Collection and Processing of Personal Data  
** When you visit our websites, our server automatically records the name of your Internet service provider, the website from which you visit us, the websites you actually visit and the date and length of your visit. Nissan uses cookies to follow the preferences of our visitors and optimize our websites. Additional personal data is only stored if volunteered by you, for example in the context of a registration, a survey, a contest or in execution of a contract.   
**  
Use and Disclosure of Personal Data and Purpose Specification**  
Nissan will use your personal data for the sole purpose of technical administration of the websites, customer fulfillment and administration, product surveys and marketing, only to the extent necessary in each specific case.   
We will only disclose your data to governmental authorities in cases where it is required by law. Our employees, agencies, and retailers are obliged by us to respect confidentiality and abide by Codes of Conduct of Nissan. 

**Freedom of Choice  
** We may use your data to inform you about our products and services and, where applicable, request your opinion. Naturally, your participation is completely voluntary. Should you not consent, you can inform us at any time by postal letter, so that we can specifically prohibit the use of your data. Please refer to local brand site services for further instructions. 

**Freedom of Information  
** Upon written request, Nissan or its retailers will inform you by letter what personal data are stored by us as defined by local law. If such data are incorrect, we will correct that information at your request. Please refer to local brand site services for further instructions. 

**Security  
** Nissan uses technical and organizational security measures to protect the data we have under our control against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction or against access by unauthorized persons. Our security procedures are continually enhanced as new technology becomes available.
